Preliminary Inventory to the Bernard and Jewel Bellush Papers WAG.030
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Bernard and Jewel Bellush Papers
1947-2002
1960-1990
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Bellush, Jewel, 1924-
Bellush, Bernard, 1917-
WAG.030
20 Linear Feet (20 boxes)
Jewel and Bernard Bellush are historians and political activists, who taught for many years at the City College of New York. In the late 1970s, at the request of Council executive director Victor Gotbaum, they became engaged in a collaborative project to write a history of AFSCME, District Council 37, the umbrella group for local unions representing many categories of public employees in the city of New York. The Bellushes' book, Union Power and New York: Victor Gotbaum and District Council 37 was published in 1984. The first part of the collection consists of correspondence, background files, interviews, flyers, notes and drafts for the book. The second part of the collection is comprised of files on Americans for Democratic Action, the Socialist Party, the New York Labor History Association and many other organizations in which Bernard Bellush was active or took an interest. It also includes topical files on many political and sociological issues, and files of personal and biographical material.
Custodial History
The initial donation of research files of Jewel and Bernard Bellush to the Tamiment Library/Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives was made in the fall of 1984. The materials in this portion of the collection were compiled by Jewel and Bernard Bellush during the writing of their published study, Union Power and New York: Victor Gotbaum and District Council 37 (Praeger, 1984). Many of these files contain copies of materials housed in District Council 37 offices and storage facilities, to which the Bellushes were given access. Some sensitive materials were removed by the Bellushes prior to transferring the collection to NYU. The accession number associated with these materials is 1984.013.
A second donation of material, consisting of more general files of political, personal and research materials, was made by Bernard Bellush in 2002.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Historical/Biographical Note
Jewel Lubin Bellush, a native of Brooklyn, was born on May 20, 1924. She attended new York City public schools, including Samuel J. Tilden High School. After a brief stay at City College, she went to the University of Wisconsin at Madison, majoring in American history and graduating in 1946. In February 1946 she entered the graduate program in American history at Columbia University, where she met her future husband, Bernard Bellush. She earned a masters degree, with a thesis on "Women and Abolition," and a Ph.D., with a dissertation on Herbert H. Lehman.
After graduate school she taught at City College (evening session) and was later appointed to a tenured position at Hunter College, in the Political Science Department. She was also a Fulbright Professor at the University of Haifa in Israel. She wrote, or collaborated with others on, a number of studies of political parties and urban planning. A lifelong community activist, she continued her lecturing and political involvement after retirement.
Bernard Bellush was born in New York City on November 15, 1917 and reared in the Bronx. He also attended the public schools of New York City and graduated from City College in 1941. He served in the army from 1942 to 1945, taking part in the landing on Omaha Beach. After the War he earned a master's degree in history at Columbia University, with a thesis on Eugene V. Debs, and a Ph.D., with a dissertation on Franklin D. Roosevelt as governor of New York.
Bernard Bellush taught American history at Hunter College and then received a tenured appointment at City College, where he served as first Chairman of the Faculty Senate. He also served as a Fulbright Professor at the University of Utrecht in the Netherlands. He published several books in American history. His civic activism is reflected in his having served as a National Board member of the American Veterans Committee; a city, state and national Board member of Americans for Democratic Action; a member of the NGO Committee on Disarmament, Peace and Security; and a Board member and President of the New York Labor History Association. He died on December 30, 2011.
The Bellushes were married in June of 1947. It was a "mixed marriage," as Bernie was a stalwart of the Socialist Party and Jewel came from a Communist Party background. Political acquaintances were inclined to believe that the union would be short-lived, but a harmonious and productive partnership spanning more than sixty years ensued. The most significant concrete evidence of this collaboration is their jointly written book, Union Power and New York, a history of AFSCME District Council 37. Research materials, interviews and drafts associated with that project make up the first six series of this collection. After serving for a year as a staff member in the Education Department of District 37 in the late 1970s, Bernie Bellush returned to teaching. At this point he was asked by DC 37 Executive Director Victor Gotbaum to write a history of the District Council. The project quickly grew to such proportions that Bernie enlisted the help of Jewel; the couple soon retired from teaching and devoted themselves intensively to completing the manuscript, which was finally published in 1984.
District Council 37 was chartered by the American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME) in November 1944. At that time its membership was limited to small numbers in the NYC departments of Hospitals, Parks, Finance and Health. Its first goals were to increase membership and to engage management in serious collective bargaining talks. Between 1950 55, city employees gained Social Security coverage, Workmen's Compensation benefits and improved pension and health benefits. In July 1954, Mayor Robert F. Wagner Jr. signed an interim order recognizing city workers' rights to organize and at the same time setting up joint labor relations committees. A demonstration at City Hall in 1955 prompted Parks Commissioner Robert Moses to accede to a representation election in his department, which AFSCME won overwhelmingly.
The AFL CIO merger in 1955 brought many changes to the District Council. The AFL's AFSCME eventually merged with the CIO's Government and Civil Employees union. By 1957, the Government and Civic Employees New York Joint Board had been dissolved and its locals affiliated with DC 37. Among the locals thus acquired were Welfare Workers, Local 371; School Lunch Local 372; Quasi Public School Local 374 and the Civil Service Technical Guild, Local 375.
In 1958, Mayor Wagner signed Executive Order 49 giving collective bargaining rights to employee organizations representing a majority of the employees in a bargaining unit. At about that time, a series of strikes in cultural institutions resulted in union recognition for employees at Youth House, the Brooklyn Botanical Garden, the Bronx Zoo and the Coney Island Aquarium. A strike of Local 983, the Motor Vehicle Operators, resulted in the first welfare fund for non uniformed city employees, and the Council expanded its operations to service the fund. Local 372, School Lunch Employees, won bargaining rights for over 6,000 employees in 1963 and added another 6,000 in 1965. The Civil Service Technical Guild negotiated its first contract in 1963on behalf of its 5,000 engineers and architects. By 1967, the City of New York set up an Office of Collective Bargaining; in that year DC 37 reached a membership of 50,000. The first citywide contract was negotiated in 1968. Membership had grown to about 125,000 by the end of the twentieth century.
In 1964, Jerry Wurf, Executive Director of DC 37 since 1947, was elected President of AFSCME. Calogeri Taibi became the Council's new Executive Director, but served only briefly. He was succeeded by Victor Gotbaum, who retired in 1986 after a period of dynamic growth followed by historic challenges for municipal labor during the City's fiscal crisis of the mid-1970s. Stanley Hill, a former president of the Social Service Employees Union (AFSCME, Local 371) and Director of the Council's Clerical and Administrative Division, followed Gotbaum as Executive Director. In 2002, after a period of turmoil in the Council, Lillian Roberts, who had served as Assistant to Gotbaum, helped to organize 20,000 hospital workers, and left the Council to become New York State Commissioner of Labor, returned to take on the position of Executive Director.
Sources:
Bernard and Jewel Bellush, Union Power and New York: Victor Gotbaum and District Council 37 (New York: Praeger Publishers, 1984).
Scope and Content Note
The first six series, I, Early History-General Files, 1952-1981; II, Political Action, 1963-1981; III, Hospital Division and Education Department, 1956-1982; IV, New York City Fiscal Crisis, 1961-1981; V, Interview and AFSCME Local Files, 1948-1984; and VI, Chapter Drafts, undated, consists of files assembled by the Bellushes during their work on Union Power. The files contain correspondence, background files, interview transcripts, flyers, notes and drafts for the book.
Series VII, Unprocessed Political and General Files, 1947-2002, is comprised of files on Americans for Democratic Action, the Socialist Party, the New York Labor History Association and many other organizations in which Bernard Bellush was active or took an interest. It also includes topical files on many political and sociological issues, files on notable individuals in politics and labor, and files of personal and biographical material.
NOTE: This collection is stored offsite and advance notice is required for use.
Arrangement
Series V is arranged alphabetically; other series retain the original order of the material as donated.
The files are grouped into seven series:
Missing Title
I, Early History-General Files, 1952-1981
II, Political Action, 1963-1981
III, Hospital Division and Education Department, 1956-1982
IV, New York City Fiscal Crisis, 1961-1981
V, Interview and AFSCME Local Files, 1948-1984
VI, Chapter Drafts, undated
VII, Unprocessed Political and General Files, 1947-2002.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by Bernard Bellush, 1984. The accession number associated with this gift is 1984.013. An additional donation was made in 2002.
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers. Materials not yet digitized will need to have access copies made before they can be used. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu, (212) 998-2630 with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Government employee unions |z United States.; Municipal officials and employees |x Labor unions |z New York (State) |z New York.; White collar workers |x Labor unions |z New York (State) |z New York.; Correspondence.; Hospitals |x Employees |x Labor unions |z United States.; Clippings (information artifacts); Drafts (documents); Transcripts.; Articles.; Minutes (administrative records); New York (N.Y.); Reports.; Fliers (printed matter); Gotbaum, Victor; Wurf, Jerry, 1919-; New York City Health and Hospitals Corporation; Americans for Democratic Action; New York Labor History Association; AFSCME. District Council 37 (New York, N.Y.); AFSCME. District Council 37 (New York, N.Y.) -- History; Congress of Industrial Organizations (U.S.). Government and Civic Employees Organizing Committee; Roberts, Lillian; Koch, Ed, 1924-2013; Bellush, Bernard, 1917-
- Series I: Early History-General Files, 1952-1981.
  - City Employee Unions, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Congress and Public Employees Strikes, Congressional Digest, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Two Faces of Unionism, The Public Interest, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Quality of Employment Survey, 1969-1977 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Security in Public Employment, Monthly Labor Review, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Union /Non-union Wage Differential, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Public Employment Bibliography, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Worker Earnings, 1967-1978 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Articles and Clippings, 1961-1981 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Labor Organizations in New York State, 1958-1978 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - AFSCME/DC 37: Articles, 1952-1964 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - DC 37: Observations on Daily Operations, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining: Background, Undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Collective Bargaining: Articles, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Wagner, Mayor Robert F.: Union Use of Premises (Correspondence, Executive Order), 1965 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Welfare Fund, DC 37: Policy, Memos, Telegrams, Correspondence, 1958-1978 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Upstate: Correspondence, 1960-1969 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Staff Union, FEU and FFR: Contracts, Correspondence, Memos, 1958-1973 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Wage-Price Freeze: Executive Council, Memos, Telegrams, Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Municipal Labor Committee: General Minutes, 1967-1977 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Municipal Labor Committee: Steering Committee Minutes, 1967-1981 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Collective Bargaining: Correspondence, 1956-1974 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Municipal Labor Committee/Office of Collective Bargaining, 1970-1978 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Collective Bargaining-Tripartite Panel: Correspondence, Statements, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Citywide Contracts, 1967-1973 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Jerry Wurf/Carter Negotiations: Flyer, Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Taylor Law: Public Hearing Minutes, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Charts for Bureaucracy Chapter, Undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Bureaucracy: Background Notes, Undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Bureaucracy: Sources, Undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Divisions in DC 37: Memos, Correspondence, 1965-1973 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Divisions Directors: Interviews, 1978-1982 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Staff of DC 37: Correspondence, Research, 1965-1969 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Staff Reports, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Wurf Reorganizes AFSCME: Research, Correspondence, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Union Members: Research, 1962-1964 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - International Convention: Printed Material, 1958-1964 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - AFSCME: Correspondence, 1958-1965 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Judicial Panel: Rules, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Constitutional Changes Under Wurf: Constitution, Correspondence, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Executive Board Minutes, 1965-1966, 1969-1970, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Joe Sperling, Local 371: Correspondence, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Staff and Organization Status: Charts, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Staff Reports to Gotbaum: Memos, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Series II: Political Action, 1963-1981.
  - Political Action: Flyers, Correspondence, Memos, 1966-1974 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Political Action: Correspondence, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Political Chapter Footnotes, Undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Pension Rejection/Bridge and Sewer Strike: Memos, Correspondence, Research, Reports, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Pension Footnotes: Notes, Articles, Correspondence, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Agency Shop: Correspondence, Agreements, Notes, 1964-1977 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Retirees Association: Reports, Newsletters, Correspondence, 1978-1980 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Retirees Memoirs: Correspondence, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Political Participation Sources: Notes, Reports, 1977-1981 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Political Action, Legislative Committee: Minutes, Correspondence, 1957-1966 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Wagner, Robert F., Jr.: Correspondence, Telegrams, 1961-1962 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Strikes: Views by Others (articles), 1970, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - UFT Strike and Leadership: Correspondence, Articles, Telegrams, Notes, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Local 420 Campaign and Elections: Correspondence, Newsletter, Telegrams, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Local 237, Agreements, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - CETA-How It Works: Report, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - NYS AFL-CIO Convention-Gubernatorial Endorsement: Article, Correspondence, Printed Material, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - New York State Governors: Memos, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Public Interest Contributions: Correspondence, Articles, Reports, 1963-1972 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Political Action Dept.: Memos, Lists, Reports, Correspondence, Printed Material, 1962-1981 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - C.O.U.R.S.: Correspondence, Flyers, 1961-1963, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Political Action and Campaign Course, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - DC 37 Third Women's Conference: Printed Material, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - School Board Elections: Correspondence, Flyers, Reports, 1973-1977 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Jewish Labor Committee: Minutes, Telegrams, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Political Interviews: Notes, Undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - DC 37 Political Survey: Reports, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Beyond Bread and Butter: Report, Correspondence, Undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Baim Study of DC 37 Workers' Attitudes: Reports, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - OSHA Bill: Draft, Report, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Gotbaum and Congress: Correspondence, 1971-1974 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - National Presidential Nomination: Correspondence, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - March on Washington: Flyers, Correspondence, 1963, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Vietnam: Telegrams, Correspondence, Flyers, 1968-1972 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Series III: Hospital Division and Education Department, 1956-1982.
  - Hospital Affiliation: Correspondence, Legal Docket, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - HHC Ethnic Identity Managerial/Supervisory Titles: Charts, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - A Campaign to Organize Hospital Employees: Notes, Undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - HHC and Lillian Roberts: Correspondence, 1970-1974 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Personal Services Unit: Reports, Memos, Tables, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - United WREP Workers: Dockets, Correspondence, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Bio med Program: Correspondence, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Fiscal Crisis Impact on Staff and Membership: Memos, Reports, 1974-1978 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Hospital Crisis: Correspondence, Reports, 1974-1976 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Hospitals: Budgets, Correspondence, Reports, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Roberts, Lillian: Africa and Israel, Memos, 1974-1978 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Family Care Centers: Press Release, Correspondence, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Correspondence, Reports, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - National Health Insurance and Union Health Plans: Memos, Reports, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - CETA: Correspondence, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Municipal Labor Committee: Correspondence, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - HHC: Reports, Correspondence, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Health Systems (NYC): New York Affairs, Article, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Statements on Hospital Situation: Report, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Kennedy Hearing on National Health Insurance: Transcript, Correspondence, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Koch's Health Plan: Report, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - HHC: Reports, 1979-1982 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Hospital Closing: NAACP, Telegrams, Correspondence, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Butler Affair: Notes, Memos, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Education: Notes and Footnotes, Undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Health Is Everybody's Business: Report, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Health and Safety: newsletters, flyers, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Education Fund: reports, memos, notes, 1968-1985 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Counseling: interview notes, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - College of New Rochelle: articles, correspondence, notes, 1973-1981 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Career Development: articles, correspondence, reports, 1966-1975 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Retirees: newsletters, notes, articles, 1968-1982 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Conferences: notes, correspondence, 1956-1981 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Mann's Education: reports, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Education Department Activities: articles, memos, reports, correspondence, 1967-1978 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Labor Education: memos, correspondence, notes, 1968-1982 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Education Interviews: notes, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Series IV: New York City Fiscal Crisis, 1961-1981.
  - Health and Securities Plan: Minutes, Articles, Reports, 1963-1978 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Municipal Employee Legal Services (MELS): Ford Foundation Report, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - MELS: Reports, Notes, 1981-1984 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - A Union Saves the City, Chapter Outline: Notes, Undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - DC 37 and Fiscal Crisis: Reports, Articles, Notes, Undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Fiscal Crisis: Notes, Reports, Undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Budget Crisis: Reports, Correspondence, 1969-1971 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Emergency Employment Act: Reports, Correspondence, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - State Politics: Articles, Correspondence, 1966-1973 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - NYC Politics: Notes, Articles, Correspondence, 1961-1981 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Fiscal Crisis: Articles, Correspondence, Notes, 1974-1977 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - NYC Fiscal History: Reports, Correspondence, 1976-1979 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Employment/Unemployment: Reports, Articles, 1972, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Municipal Unions/Financial Leaders: Minutes, 1977-1979 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Pension Fund: Correspondence, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Economic Forecasts: Memos, Reports, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Emergency Financial Control Board.: Correspondence, Reports, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Koch, Edward: Notes, Reports, Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Zander Housing Project: Hearing Transcripts, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Series V: Interview and AFSCME Local Files, 1948-1984.
  - Adler, Norman, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Ames, Joe, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Baron, Irving, Undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Bigel, Jack, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Bilik, Al, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Boer, John, 1944, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Casamo, William, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Cohen, Bart, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Diop, Al, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Feinstein, Barry, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Flaxer, Abram, Undated (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Gordon, Murray, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Gotbaum, Sarah, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Gotbaum, Victor (Biography by Rosenberg), Undated (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Gotbaum, Victor, 1970, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Handman, Question, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Hughes, Charles, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Kiefer, Mildred, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Kramer, Leo, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Lindenthal, Nat, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Lustig, Richard, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Maher, Edward, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Perkel, Bertram "Buddy", 1982 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Reif, Elliot, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Roberts, Lillian, Undated (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Rose, Bert, Undated (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Ross, Phil, Undated (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Schleicher, Bill, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Shalala, Donna, Undated (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Staff interviews, Undated (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Shanker, Albert, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Stephens, Bernie, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Topol, Julius, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Toto, John and Gary Foster, 1978-1980 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Varner, Louis, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Viani, Alan, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Wright, Lester, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Wurf, Jerome "Jerry", 1974-1979 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Wurf, Jerome "Jerry", 1982 (Box 5, Folder 7)